Adam Mayer

Perth, Western Australia

| Phone: 0466 556 976 | Email: acmd.games@gmail.com LinkedIn: /in/adam-mayer-diamond | GitHub: /ACMayer

SUMMARY

A hardworking, analytical and energised Data Professional with background in Exercise and Sports Science. My strengths are attention to detail, creative problem solving, leadership and innovation.

9 years' experience officiating, coaching and mentoring, showing commitment and self-development.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: Python, JavaScript, HTML/CSS, SQL, NoSQL, Visual Basic, Pandas

Applications: GitHub, APIs, Git Bash, Tableau, Visual Studio Code, Jupyter Notebook, Excel

Data: PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Leaflet, TensorFlow, D3.js, BeautifulSoup, SQLAlchemy, Flask

PROJECTS

We, The New York Squirrels | https://github.com/ACMayer/We-The-Squirrels

Produced an interactive dashboard depicting a squirrel's day-to-day life in New York City using annual squirrel census data.

Role: Data analyst and interpreter

- Languages (and Libraries): Python (Pandas, Flask), SQL Alchemy, JavaScript (Leaflet, D3.js), HTML/CSS
- Tools: Git Bash, Jupyter Notebook

Crowdfunding | https://github.com/ACMayer/Crowdfunding-ETL

Performed data pre-processing using Python and converted into a Panda's data frame. Output as SQL schema

Role: Data analyst

- Languages (and Libraries): Python (Pandas)
- Tools: Git Bash, Jupyter Notebook

Project 4 | https://github.com/ACMayer/Project4-MNIST

Classified medical images through a machine learning model using the MNIST dataset on Kaggle, with the goal to identify diseases.

- Role: Data analyst
- Languages (and Libraries): Python (pandas, pathlib, numpy, matplotlib) SKlearn, Keras, Tensorflow,
 Pillow
- Tools: Git Bash, Jupyter Notebook, Power Point, Streamlit

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Football Coach / Mentor UWA, Stirling Macedonia, Subiaco AFC

2017 - Present

- Planned, organised, and delivered training sessions tailored to development and match performance.
- Analysed game and training footage to present to players and coaches.
- Mentored adult and youth players.
- Communicated with stakeholders in various mediums in a clear concise and timely manner.
- Organised referees and pitches to ensure adequate space available for matches.

Onsite Medical Care (Short-term contract) Administration Support

- 2/2021 6/2021
- Provided administration support while the company prepared for accreditation by the Australian Health Standards Association.
- Performed daily administration duties to assist the clinical and management teams, including answering phone calls, corresponding with specialists and other external providers, scanning and filing.
- Database entry including medical records, with a focus on patient confidentiality.
- Created patient files and information packs, including health information, feedback forms and surveys.

Various Basketball Leagues including state level Referee, Referee Coach / Mentor

2013 - 2020

- eree, Referee Coach / Mentor
- Analysed game footage for referee teaching purposes.
- Mentored players and coaches in application and interpretation of official rules.
- Created development plans and provided mentoring for referees.
- Collaborated in designing assessment criteria for referees.
- Organising and scheduled referees for both regular season and finals fixtures.
- Communicated with a variety of stakeholders, including other officials, players, coaches score bench, and spectators.
- Focused on objectivity and impartiality in often difficult and passionate situations.

EDUCATION

Data Analytics Certificate, University of Western Australia	Perth, 2024
Bachelor of Science (Exercise & Sports Science), Edith Cowan	Perth, 2014 - 2018

OTHER PROFESSIONAL EDUCATION

Football Federation Australia Certificates

•	FFA B Licence Coaching	Perth, 2020 - 2021
•	FFA C Licence Coaching	Perth, 2018

Basketball Western Australia Certificates

•	Level 1 Basketball Referee	Perth, 2014
•	Level 1 Basketball Referee Coach	Perth, 2016